resumeinvideo.com 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy | The best professional resume writing service

The Privacy Policy, the provisions of which are described below, is a legal tool designed to oversee your and our behaviors in regards to the interaction with the website and any connected services.

This legally binding document governs our relations concerning only privacy. By accepting to be bound legally by this document, you enter into an agreement with us. Consequently, both you and us are to have mutual legal rights and obligations.

As you open our website in any browser on any device you automatically provide your consent to the provisions of this document and become legally bound by it. If you disagree with any of the points mentioned within this Privacy Policy and do not wish to be bound by it, please leave the website and do not order any of our services.

The Privacy Policy applies to your actions throughout the complete use of our website.

## General Provisions

We strive to provide you with the service and experience at the highest level. For that to be possible, we deem it required to implement an easy, yet, authentic procedure of identification. In addition to that, specific manners of communication and available options to you are set up.

While you use our service, only particular details are collected from our side. This is done in order to improve the usage of our website by users and to make their experience the best possible.

By expressing your consent with this Privacy Policy, you agree that the goal of collecting particular details about you is specified adequately, that it is explicit and legitimate. Moreover, you also agree to provide us with correct, comprehensive, applicable and up-to-date information when interacting with our service.

The information that we collect based on the provisions of this Privacy Policy is seen as gathered honestly and lawfully. No details about you are gathered without obtaining your prior explicit consent. 

Most of the information we gather is submitted by you personally. However, we may collect certain details by ourselves with your agreement.

Details that are provided by you:

  * details submitted into surveys / questionnaires / forms;
  * details provided by you through communication with our Support Team;
  * details about the identification of your personality.

The details we gather are collected by:

  * examining your interaction with our website and activity on it,
  * tracking the transactions made to our website;
  * implementing cookie files and other related technologies.

The following details are never collected by us:

  * your sexual orientation,
  * your views on politics,
  * your religious, philosophical or any different related beliefs,
  * your physical or mental health conditions,
  * any of your criminal convictions.

## Details collected while you visit our website

As soon as you visit any page of our Website from a particular device with the use of a specific browser, some details are automatically collected. They include:

  * type of your browser;
  * your operating system;
  * time of access.

These details do not give us the possibility to identify you in any way. Moreover, we do not pursue to do so or to expose the personalities of our website visitors in no way.

However, we need to collect such details in order to improve our website content and customize it for the needs of our visitors. The information collected in such a way also allows us to adjust the layout and design of our pages so they are legible for you to view.

## Details collected while you purchase our services

When you wish to not only visit our website, but also place an order for our service, we ask you provide specific information for the required order to be completed for you just the way you need it. The following details are collected once you order with us:

  * your email address,
  * your telephone number,
  * last 4 digits of your credit card, its type and the name on it,
  * a copy of your driver’s license or national ID provided by you only.

We use the email provided to notify you about the status of your order, any questions we or the writer may have, including clarifications and unread messages. By clicking the “proceed to payment” button, you express your sufficient consent to also get emails and/or SMS with our latest discounts, special offers and promotional materials. 

In order for us to properly authorize your payment and protect you from possible fraud, you may be asked to provide a copy of your driver’s license or national ID (with only your name visible) together with your credit card information (including only the last 4 digits, name on the card and credit card type). If the payment was made through an online system and not with a credit card, a payment receipt may be asked to be provided.

## Cookie Files

In order to improve your experience with our website, we use cookies. To learn more about such cookie files, please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.resumeformat2015.com/cookie-policy.html).

## Ways of Communication

When we gather and make use of the collected personal details, we do our best to meet the highest standards of quality. Consequently, any reported complains are treated with the utmost importance. If you believe that the information or manner in which we collect it is not fair, deceitful or unsuitable, we encourage you to inform us about this. Any and all suggestions are always welcome.

If you need any additional details or explanations, please send your request to [support@resumeformat2015.com](mailto:support@resumeformat2015.com) .

Our goal is to be as open as possible about any personal information we store. You can ask about any personal details that we may hold by sending a “subject access request” as mentioned under the Data Protection Act of 1998. In cases when we do hold certain information connected with you, we will:

  * provide a description of the information;
  * inform you about the reasons as to why we are storing it;
  * let you know who it can be disclosed to;
  * provide you with a copy of the details in an intelligible form.

When submitting your request for personal information, please put it in written form by sending an email to our Customer Support Team - [support@resumeformat2015.com](mailto:support@resumeformat2015.com).

In order to opt out of any SMS or email notifications, please [contact us](https://www.resumeformat2015.com/about-us.html). Upon getting your request, we will stop sending you the notifications within 10 business days.

## Final provisions

The SSL-certificate used to process all of the information submitted to the order and/or inquiry forms guarantees full confidentially of your information and the safety of all the transactions submitted through these forms.

To restrict access of any third-party to the collected personal details of our clients, we shall take all reasonable efforts. Our employees are to be properly instructed and trained to keep the safety of provided information. Should any lawful obligations require us to disclose any collected details, we will be required to do so.

This Privacy Policy document forms a complete understanding between you and us. Neither party of the agreement, nor you, nor us, shall have confidence in any oral or written details not expressly included in this Privacy Policy.

If any implementations of the previsions of this document are failed to be enforced, this is not to waiver any rights to enforce any of such other provisions of this document later.

Notices and reports of this document are to be considered as learned and read when 1 day passes from the moment the report or notice was sent.

No point or provision of this Privacy Policy is to set up any type of partnership/joint venture, employer-employee relationship between you and us. Moreover, nor you nor us are to be allowed to act as an agent for each other or to enter into any agreement or contract for each other as a representative of any kind.

No third party obtains any legal rights from this document, nor does any provision of this policy gives any obligations to any third party.

Our mutual communications shall be conducted only in the English language. All available means of communication can be used to inform us of any requests, inquiries, concerns or applications.

If it so happens that any particular provision of this Privacy Policy is found unenforceable, the provision is to be changed and understood in an alternative way to correspond to the needed nature of this point as much as possible.

Headings were included in this document to improve the legibility of this Privacy Policy. Keep in mind that the content and meaning of the terms indicated under each of the headings are not limited only to the sense of the heading itself. While an interpretation is made of the Privacy Policy, headings are not to be taken into account.

The legislation of the United Kingdom is the only legal system to be applicable to any arising relations from this Privacy Policy.

This document may be changed, adjusted, revised at our absolute and sole discretion with any issued notices or warnings.

The agreement of the Privacy Policy is concluded in electronic form, which equals in legislative force to that signed in ink.
